Finding Aid for David V. Tinder Collection of Michigan Photography, County File, Wayne County, 1865-1985
William L. Clements Library, University of Michigan
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 8 (Box 8)
  - 134.53-134.78 [Misc. portraits-men], 26 of 78 photographs
  - 135. [Portrait Carte De Visite-G. S. Lyons, ca. 1870s], 1 photograph
  - 136. [Jesse Lynn McKee, General Manager, Michigan Central Railroad, ca. 1925], 1 photograph
  - 137. [Joan Baxter and her hot dog cooker], 1 photograph
  - 138. [Unidentified man on horse, appears to be 20th century enlargement of earlier image], 1 photograph
  - 139. [Frank D. Fitzgerald, Michigan Secretary of State, ca. 1933 also a photocopy of tintype of his mother as a young child housed with cased images], 1 photograph, 1 photocopy
  - 140. [Hand-painted albumen portraits], 3 photographs
  - 141. [1860s Hawley family portraits including Detroit resident Elijah Hawley, also portrait of Giles Hawley Collins with written enlargement instructions ca. 1901], 3 photographs
  - 142. [Studio portrait of Zachariah Chandler, ca. 1880], 1 photograph
  - 143. [Knights Templar portraits], 2 photographs
  - Portraits -- Groups
  - 144. [Worker group portraits], 21 photographs
  - 145.1-145.11 [Miscellaneous family groups], 11 of 19 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 9 (Box 9)
  - Portraits -- Groups (cont.)
  - 145.12-145.19 [Miscellaneous family groups], 8 of 19 photographs
  - 146. [Three different years of women at Christmas party, possibly Ford Motor Company secretaries, ca. 1939-1941], 4 photographs
  - 147. [Miscellaneous portraits-couples], 15 photographs
  - 148. [Firefighters with horse drawn wagon, ca. 1890], 1 photograph
  - 149. City Council of Hamtramck 1922-23, 1 photograph
  - 150. [Michigan Photographic Historical Society members, ca. 1970s], 1 photograph
  - 151. [Farm workers with steam threshing machine, ca. 1900-1910], 2 photographs
  - 152. [General Motors, wives Christmas party, December 21, 1944], 3 photographs
  - 153. Nut Club of Detroit, August 1909, 1 photograph
  - 154. [German Club members, ca. 1910s], 1 photograph
  - 155. [Unidentified African-American man with Paul Robeson; and with "Detroit's first black judge"], 2 photographs
  - 156. Susterka Lake [ca. 1900-1910], 1 photograph
  - 157. [Business and fraternal groups], 12 photographs
  - 158. [African American group in Scott Auditorium, ca. 1941], 1 photograph
  - 159. Paramount Club, November 26, 1931 [African American society], 1 photograph
  - 160. [Banquet-Wolverine Consistory, S.P.R.S., African-American group, October 28, 1922], 1 photograph
  - 161. "The Bachelors" at the Oriental [African-American group dinner, December 24, 1917], 1 photograph
  - 162. Burning the mortgage of the Phyllis Wheatley Home, Detroit, January 4, 1915 [Phyllis Wheatley home for aged colored ladies], 1 photograph
  - 163. American Red Cross Society [African-American group, ca. 1918], 1 photograph
  - 164. Wallis-Wainwright Hack Post no.314 Past Commanders [Composite portrait, ca. 1940], 1 photograph
  - 165. A conference beginning of Older Boys and Older Girls in Detroit auspices of Y.W.C.A. and Y.M.C.A. March 23-35, 1923 [African-American group], 1 photograph
  - 166. [Direct Credits Society 1st Economic District of Michigan, ca. 1930s], 1 photograph, 1 ephemera
  - 167.1-167.23 [Miscellaneous groups], 23 of 39 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 10 (Box 10)
  - Portraits -- Groups (cont.)
  - 167.24-167.39 [Miscellaneous groups], 16 of 39 photographs
  - Portraits -- Children
  - 168. [Portrait of boy on pony, ca. 1920], 1 photograph
  - 169. [Caucasian girl with African-American doll, ca. 1940s], 1 photograph
  - 170. [Miscellaneous portraits-infants], 31 photographs
  - 171.1-171.26 [Miscellaneous portraits-children], 26 of 64 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 11 (Box 11)
  - Portraits -- Children (cont.)
  - 171.27-171.64 [Miscellaneous portraits-children], 38 of 64 photographs
  - Portraits -- Weddings
  - 172.1-172.30. [Wedding portraits], 30 of 64 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 12 (Box 12)
  - Portraits -- Weddings (cont.)
  - 172.31-172.64. [Wedding portraits], 34 of 64 photographs
  - Portraits -- Confirmation & Communion
  - 173.1-173.13 [Confirmation and Communion portraits], 13 of 41 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 13 (Box 13)
  - Portraits -- Confirmation & Communion (cont.)
  - 173.14-173.41 [Confirmation and Communion portraits], 28 of 41 photographs
  - Parades
  - 174. [American Legion parade, ca. 1951], 9 photographs
  - 175. [Republican parade, ca. 1890s], 4 photographs
  - 176. [Grand Army of the Republic Parade, ca. 1891], 4 photographs
  - 177. [Shriner's Parade, ca. 1890s], 3 photographs
  - 178. [Knights Templar parade, ca. 1910s], 1 photograph
  - 179. [United Spanish War Veterans Parade ca. 1940], 19 photographs
  - 180. [Miscellaneous parades], 14 photographs
  - Business & Commerce
  - 181. [Nicolai family collection, business exteriors (horse shoeing, blacksmith, and real estate) and automobiles, ca. 1880s-1920s], 6 photographs, 1 ephemera)
  - 182. [Improved Cummer engine, ca. 1883], 1 photograph
  - 183. Boat Transit Company [ca. 1930s-1940s], 4 photographs, 1 ephemera
  - 184. [Jacob F. Meier Co, factory and automobile, ca. 1910], 7 photographs
  - 185. [D.H. Burrell & Co.-Hoop cutting], 10 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 14 (Box 14)
  - Business & Commerce (cont.)
  - 186. [Marx Brewing Co.], 3 photographs, 1 booklet
  - 187. [Turbine engine-Pennsylvania Salt Manufacturing Co., ca. 1925-27], 4 photographs
  - 188. [Dodge Brothers employee rallies, ca. 1917-1920], 10 photographs
  - 189. [Detroit Dredging Co.], 4 photographs
  - 190. [Miscellaneous commercial photos, products, buildings, equipment, interiors], 37 photographs
  - 191. [Paired photographs showing both exteriors and interiors of miscellaneous businesses], 13 photographs
  - 192. [Candler Dock & Dredge Co. Workers, ca.1920s-1930s], 1 photograph
  - 193. C.M. Nichols, Honey Producer [display booth, ca. 1910], 1 photograph
  - Business & Commerce -- Business Exteriors
  - 194. [Display window at Hudson's, September 15, 1953], 1 photograph
  - 195. [Woodworth's and S.S. Kresge Co. storefronts in Plymouth, Mich, ca. 1950-51], 2 photographs
  - 196. [Exterior of W. E. Barker & Co ca. 1890s, December 19, 1914 newspaper clipping concerning store of H. B. Barker & Sons], 2 photographs, 1 ephemera
  - 197. David Stott's flour mill [ca. 1890-95], 1 photograph
  - 198. [Miscellaneous business exteriors], 46 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 15 (Box 15)
  - Business & Commerce -- Business Interiors
  - 199. Leon G. Nahnikian Expert Shoe Repairing shop [Hat cleaning and shoe repair shop, ca. 1919], 3 photographs
  - 200. [Unidentified shoe repair shop and employee, ca. 1922], 1 photograph
  - 201. [Sharpe's Cafeteria interiors, ca. 1938], 2 photographs
  - 202. [Hoffman's store, Detroit, Mich. ca. 1925-1935], 5 photographs
  - 203. [Candy aisle at Kresge's, ca. 1950], 4 photographs
  - 204. [Women in R.G. Dunn cigar factory, ca. 1909], 1 photograph
  - 205. [Factory interior-women workers, ca. 1920s-1930s], 1 photograph
  - 206. [Briggs Manufacturing-auto bodies, George Slauson foreman, ca. 1920s], 4 photographs
  - 207. [Miscellaneous store interiors, incl. African-American grocery store], 31 photographs
  - 208. [Misc. interior views of businesses, incl. African-American restaurant], 21 photographs
  - 209. [Miscellaneous industrial interiors], 53 photographs
  - Business & Commerce -- Construction
  - 210. [Stewart's Ladies Wear store renovation, ca. 1920s], 2 photographs
  - 211. [Trenton Channel Powerhouse construction, ca. 1924], 8 photographs
  - 212. [Briggs Manufacturing Co. factory site, ca. 1920], 4 photographs
  - 213. [St. Paul Gas Light Co. construction, ca. 1911], 2 photographs
  - 214. [Unidentified building construction at 474 Montclair Ave, Detroit, May 15, 1911], 1 photograph
  - 215. McLouth Steel Corp.-stainless expansion, February 13, 1954, 1 photograph
  - 216. [Panorama of construction of artificial gas plant, ca. 1920s], 1 photograph
  - 217. [Penobscot Building construction, ca. 1928], 3 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 16 (Box 16)
  - Business & Commerce -- Ford Motor Company
  - 218. [Ford Motor Co., River Rouge industries, ca. 1925], 2 panoramic photographs
  - 219. [Ford Motor Company News Bureau photos, ca. 1946], 2 photographs
  - 220. [Miscellaneous factory and production views], 15 photographs
  - Views -- Street
  - 221. [Dearborn Coach Co., Dearborn street view, ca. 1935], 1 photograph
  - 222. [Winter storm damage, December 5, 1898], 2 photographs
  - 223. [Woodward Avenue views, ca. 1870s], 2 photographs
  - 224. [Miscellaneous street views], 23 photographs
  - Views -- Residential
  - 225. [Ulysses S. Grant headquarters, Detroit, ca. 1870], 1 photograph
  - 226. Grosse Pointe and Grosse Pointe Farms residential architecture], 4 photographs
  - 227. [Residence and garden, ca. 1912-16], 9 photographs
  - 228. [Miscellaneous Wayne County residential architecture], 4 photographs
  - 229. [Detroit residential architecture], 33 photographs
  - Views -- Aerial
  - 230. [Detroit and bridge view], 1 photograph
  - 231. [Eastwood park-aerial photo, ca. 1940s], 1 photograph
  - 232. [Miscellaneous aerial photos-Detroit], 5 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 17 (Box 17)
  - Architecture
  - 233. "Former home of William H. Yawkey" [related to estate lawsuit and investigation], 1 photograph
  - 234. Sprinkler Tank-6164 Cass Avenue [ca. 1945], 1 photograph
  - 235. [George Degens International Exposition House, Springwells, Mich., 1889], 1 photograph
  - 236. [Detroit public buildings-City Hall and Library, ca. 1880s], 2 photographs
  - 237. [Spanish American War Memorial], 1 photograph
  - 238. [Russell House Hotel, ca. 1870s], 1 photograph
  - 239. [Dearborn residential and public architecture], 24 photographs
  - 240. [Miscellaneous Wayne County architecture], 36 photographs
  - 241. [1889 Detroit International Exposition main building], 1 photograph
  - 242. Tiger Stadium, June 20, 1984, 1 photograph
  - Labor & Unemployment
  - 243. Basement of Detroit City Hall, ca. 1930, 1 photograph
  - 244. [Copy print of Peter Brooks photo of unemployed man holding sign asking for work not charity, 1930], 1 photograph
  - 245. [Woolworth Five and Ten female employees on strike, ca. 1937], 1 photograph
  - 246. [United Auto Workers strikers, musicians, ca. 1940s], 1 photograph
  - 247. [Street view of Inkster, Mich., also people lined up outside of a soup kitchen, ca. 1930s], 2 photographs
  - 248. [Journeymen Bakers International Union strikers, 1902], 1 photograph
  - 248.1. [Wives of United Automobile Workers on strike, 1939], 1 photograph
  - Athletes & Athletics
  - 249. Cass Tech High School girls sports team [ca. 1930], 1 photograph
  - 250. [Detroit Turners, mens volleyball team, ca. 1939], 2 photographs
  - 251. [Young women in swimming gear at Detroit Yacht Club posing with Olympic champion Arne Borg from Sweden, ca. 1930], 1 photograph
  - 252. [Young women's figure skating team, ca. 1920s], 1 photograph
  - 253. [Unidentified shirtless man flexing large muscles, ca. 1910], 1 photograph
  - 254. [Detroit Urban Railway baseball team and streetcar, ca. 1903-04], 1 photograph
  - 255. [Young women's field hockey team, ca. 1930], 1 photograph
  - 256. Detroit Red Wings 1938-39, 1 photograph
  - 257. [Contact sheet with images of African-Americans including Muhammad Ali [Cassius Clay], ca. 1960s], 12 photographs on a single sheet
  - 258. Jr. [Basketball] Team Barbour Int. School 1927, 1 photograph
  - 259. [Well's Roller Hockey Club, ca. 1943], 1 photograph
  - 260. [Unidentified Dearborn football player in practice gear, ca. 1940s], 1 photograph
  - 261. [Detroit Tigers group photograph, ca. 1910s], 1 photograph
  - 262. [Participants in bowling leagues, 1932-41], 2 photographs
  - 263. [Wyandotte football teams], 2 photographs
  - 264. [Detroit Tigers training room, ca. 1930s], 6 photographs, 2 negatives
  - 265. [Michigan Alkali F. C. soccer team, ca. 1923], 3 photographs
  - 266. [Wyandotte baseball teams], 4 photographs
  - 267. [Detroit Post Office baseball teams, undated and ca. 1933], 2 photographs
  - 268. [Hugh Thompson, cross country runner, ca. 1940s], 1 photograph
  - 269. [Polo match action shots, ca. 1922], 2 photographs
  - 270. [Who's Your Tailor?-basketball team, ca. 1917-18], 1 photograph
  - 271. Rose Morgan 2nd heat [horse race, ca. 1929], 1 photograph
  - 272. [Miscellaneous athletic teams], 6 photographs
  - 273. [Portrait of curling team, ca. 1943], 2 photographs
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 18 (Box 18)
  - Classrooms & Schools
  - 274. Michigan Barber College, Detroit, March 10, 1950 [African-American group], 1 photograph
  - 275. Detroit Commercial College [student group, ca. 1921], 1 photograph
  - 276. The Seniorette [yearbook, Northville High School ca. 1911], 1 booklet
  - 277. [Redford High School R.O.T.C., girls with band drum, ca. 1939], 1 photograph
  - 278. [Exterior of school, District no. 2, Dearborn Township, ca. 1920s], 1 photograph
  - 279. [Lincoln Park High School, " January Class of 1936" composite portrait in album owned by Stephen Modos with personal snapshots and autographs of classmates], 10 photographs
  - 280. [Miscellaneous school group portraits], 23 photographs
  - Places of Worship & Religious Activities
  - 281. [Bar Mitzvah luncheon, January 18, 1964], 3 photographs
  - 282. [20th century studio portraits of Catholic priests], 2 photographs
  - 283. [Miscellaneous churches], 7 photograph
  - 284. [African-American A.M.E. church members dressed as African royalty, ca. 1920s], 1 photograph
  - 285. River Rouge and Delray A.M.E.A.C.E. League [African-American Group, ca. 1930], 1 photograph
  - 286. Reuniunea Femeilor SF. Treime [Romanian women's meeting at Holy Trinity Church, ca. 1920s], 1 photograph
  - 287. [Miscellaneous church and religious school groups], 26 photographs
  - 288. [Composite of exterior of New Mt. Zion Baptist Church with portrait of African-American Rev. J. S. Williams, ca. 1928], 1 photograph
  - 289. [Exterior of St. Aloysius Parish School, ca. 1920s], 1 photograph
- David V. Tinder collection of Michigan photography, County File, Wayne County, Box 19 (Box 19)
  - Parks
  - 290. [Detroit park views, July 4, 1906], 8 photographs
  - 291. [Belle Isle and Water Works Park, ca. 1911], 3 photographs
  - 292. [Electric Park and Eastwood Park, ca. 1910s-1920s], 32 photographs
  - 293. [Miscellaneous Detroit park views, ca. 1900-1920], 14 photographs
  - 294. [Water Works Park, ca. 1890s-1950s], 6 photographs
  - Parks -- Belle Isle
  - 295. [Parade on Belle Isle, ca. 1910], 2 photographs
  - 296. Fellowcraft Club, Belle Isle, June 2, 1924, 2 photographs
  - 297. [Belle Isle views ca. 1880s-1929], 42 photographs
  - 298. [Belle Isle Park features, ca. 1910s], 3 photographs
  - Funerals & Postmortem Photography
  - 299. [Post mortem-funeral displays, ca. 1910s-1930s], 14 photographs
Subjects:
David V. Tinder Collection of Michigan Photography.; Photographs shelf.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Actors--Michigan--1900-1910.; Actresses--Michigan--1890-1910.; African American businesspeople--Michigan.; African American children--Portraits--Michigan.; African American choirs--Michigan.; African American churches--Michigan.; African American freemasons--Michigan.; African American judges--Michigan.; African American musicians--Michigan.; African Americans--Societies, etc.--Michigan.; African American students--Michigan.; African American Sunday schools--Michigan.; Agricultural laborers--Michigan.; Airports--Michigan.; Aircraft--Michigan--1930-1940.; Aircraft industry--Michigan.; Air shows--Michigan.; Amateur theater--Michigan.; American Red Cross.; Amusement parks--Michigan.; Animals on television--Michigan.; Ancient Arabic Order of the Nobles of the Mystic Shrine for North America.; Asbestos--Michigan.; Automobile factories--Michigan.; Automobile industry workers--Michigan.; Automobile rallies--Michigan.; Automobiles--Michigan.; Automobiles--Design and construction--Michigan.; Balls (Parties)--Michigan--1910-1920.; Bands (Music)--Michigan.; Banquets--Michigan--1920-1930.; Barbers--Michigan.; Barbershops--Michigan--1910-1920.; Bar mitzvah--Michigan.; Bars (Drinking establishments)--Michigan.; BASF Wyandotte Corporation.; Baseball players--Michigan.; Basketball courts--Michigan.; Basketball players--Michigan.; Beauty shops--Michigan.; Beekeepers--Michigan.; Belle Isle Park (Detroit, Mich.); Bicycles & tricycles--Michigan--1890-1930.; Bicycle stores--Michigan.; Blacksmiths--Michigan.; Blizzards--Michigan.; Boats and boating--Michigan.; Boycotts--Michigan.; Breweries--Michigan.; Breweries--Employees--Michigan.; Brick trade--Michigan.; Bridges--Michigan--Detroit.; Broom and brush industry--Michigan.; Building construction--Michigan--1910-1930.; Buses--Michigan--1930-1940.; Business organizations--Michigan.; Business Schools--Michigan.; Button industry--Michigan.; Cafeterias--Michigan.; Camping--Michigan.; Canoes and canoeing--Michigan.; Cartercar Co.; Carts & wagons--Michigan--1890-1910; Casinos--Michigan.; Catholic Church--Clergy--Michigan.; Catholic schools--Michigan.; Cemeteries--Michigan.; Chauffeurs--Michigan.; Chemical industry--Michigan.; Children's costumes--Michigan.; Children's parties--Michigan--1890-1900.; Children--Michigan--Portraits.; Children's choirs--Michigan.; Church buildings--Michigan.; Cigar industry--Michigan.; Circus animals--Michigan.; Circus performers--Michigan.; City councils--Michigan--Hamtramck (Mich.); City halls--Michigan.; Commercial photography--Michigan.; Concert programs--Michigan.; Confirmation--Catholic Church--Michigan.; Construction workers--Michigan.; Coopers and Cooperage--Michigan.; Couples--Michigan--Portraits.; Creameries--Michigan.; Cross-country runners--Michigan.; Curling--Michigan.; Dairying--Michigan.; Dearborn (Mich.); Delivery of goods--Michigan.; Detroit College of Medicine.; Detroit Institute of Arts.; Detroit (Mich.); Detroit Museum of Art.; Detroit Opera House.; Detroit Red Wings (Hockey team); Detroit Symphony Orchestra.; Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad.; Diving--Michigan--1890-1900.; Docks--Michigan.; Dodge Brothers.; Dredges--Michigan.; Drugstores--Michigan.; Dwellings--Michigan.; Engines--Michigan.; Entertainers--Michigan--1900-1910.; Ethnic costume--Romania.; Ethnic groups--Michigan.; Exhibitions--Michigan--1880-1890.; Explosions--Michigan.; Factories--Employees--Michigan.; Factories--Michigan.; Families--Michigan--Portraits.; Fire fighters--Michigan.; Florists--Michigan.; Flour mills--Michigan.; Flower arrangements--Michigan--1920-1940.; Football players--Michigan--1900-1910.; Ford Motor Company.; Ford Motor Company--Employees.; Ford Motor Company. Rouge River Plant.; Ford Rotunda (Dearborn, Mich.); Fraternal organizations--Michigan; Funeral rites & ceremonies--Michigan--1910-1930; Gardens--Michigan--1900-1910.; Gas power plants--Michigan.; General Motors Corporation.; Graduation (School); Grant, Ulysses S. (Ulysses Simpson), 1822-1885--Homes and haunts.; Grocery trade--Michigan.; Hardware stores--Michigan.; Hat trade--Michigan.; Henry Ford Museum and Greenfield Village.; High school students--Michigan.; Horse-drawn rail cars--Michigan.; Horse racing--Michigan--1920-1930; Hospitals--Michigan--Detroit.; Hotels--Michigan--1870-1890.; Hudson's (Department store); Ice industry--Michigan.; Insurance companies--Michigan.; International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (CIO); Inventors--Michigan; Jazz musicians--Michigan; Journeymen Bakers National Union of the United States.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963.; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968.; Kitchen utensils--Michigan.; Knights of Pythias.; Knights Templar (Masonic order); Laboratories--Michigan.; Lakes--Michigan.; Libraries--Michigan--Detroit.; Lighthouses--Michigan.; Locomotives--Michigan.; Luggage industry--Michigan.; Mausoleums--Michigan.; Mechanical musical instruments--Michigan.; Men--Michigan--Portraits.; Men--Societies and clubs--Michigan.; Metalworking industries--Michigan.; Michigan Central Railroad Company.; Michigan. National Guard.; Michigan Stove Company.; Military bands--Michigan.; Motion pictures--Michigan--1930-1940.; Motorboat racing--Michigan.; Music stores--Michigan.; Musicians--Michigan.; Nightclubs--Michigan.; Nursing schools--Michigan.; Occupational training--Michigan.; Offices--Michigan--1910-1930.; Old age homes--Michigan.; Opticians--Michigan.; Paddle steamers--Michigan.; Parade floats--Michigan.; Parades--Michigan.; Parks--Michigan--Detroit.; Photography--Societies, etc--Michigan.; Picnics--Michigan.; Playgrounds--Michigan.; Police--Michigan--Detroit.; Police stations--Michigan.; Political parades & rallies--Michigan--1900-1920.; Portraits, group--Michigan.; Postmortem photography--Michigan.; Power-plants--Design and construction--Michigan.; Priests--Michigan.; Prisons--Michigan.; Public architecture--Michigan.; Radio broadcasting--Michigan.; Railroad stations--Michigan.; Railroad tunnels--Design and construction--Michigan.; Railroad tunnels--Michigan.; Railroads--Employees--Michigan.; Railroads--Michigan.; Residential architecture--Michigan.; Restaurants--Michigan--1920-1930.; Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976.; Sailors--Michigan.; School children--Michigan.; School buildings--Michigan.; School plays--Michigan.; School yearbooks--Michigan.; Ships--Launching--Michigan.; Ships--Michigan.; Shoes--Repairing--Michigan.; Skyscrapers--Michigan--Detroit.; Soccer players--Michigan--1920-1930; Soldiers--Michigan.; Souvenirs (Keepsakes)--Michigan.; Spanish-American War, 1898--Veterans--Michigan.; Stables--Michigan.; Steamboats--Michigan.; Steel foundries--Michigan.; Stove industry and trade--Michigan.; Street lighting--Michigan.; Street-railroads--Michigan.; Streets--Michigan.; Strikes and lockouts--Automobile industry--Michigan.; String bands--Michigan.; Storefronts--Michigan.; Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932.; Teeth--Radiography--Michigan.; Television programs--Michigan.; Theaters--Michigan--1910-1920.; Threshing machines--Michigan--1900-1910.; Tiger Stadium (Detroit, Mich.); Tour buses--Michigan.; Traffic signs & signals---Michigan--1930-1950; Train ferries--Michigan.; Trucks--Michigan--1920-1940.; Trenton Channel (Mich.); United States. Army--Recruiting, enlistment, etc.--Michigan.; United States. Army. Reserve Officers' Training Corps.; Variety stores--Michigan.; Vocational education--Michigan.; Water mills--Michigan.; Water towers--Michigan.; Waterworks--Michigan.; Wayne County (Mich.); Weddings--Michigan.; Women automobile industry workers--Michigan.; Women field hockey players--Michigan.; Women figure skaters--Michigan.; Women--Employment--Michigan--1910-1940.; Women--Michigan--Portraits.; Women--Societies and clubs--Michigan.; Woodward Avenue (Mich.); World War 1914-1918--Michigan.; YMCA of the USA.; Young Women's Christian Association.
Contributors:
Please be aware that this Contributors List is a partial index of the photographers and photographic studios represented in the collection. A complete list can be found as a pdf link in the Additional Descriptive Data section of the finding aid